Poison always leaves a trail.
Navalny is a documentary film directed by Daniel Roher.
Follows the man who survived an assassination attempt by
poisoning with a lethal nerve agent in August 2020.
During his months-long recovery, he makes shocking discoveries about
the attempt on his life and decides to return home.
Self, played by Alexei Navalny.
Self, played by Yulia Navalnaya.
Self, played by Dasha Navalnaya.
Self, played by Zakhar Navalny.
Self, played by Maria Pevchikh.
Self, played by Christo Grozev.
Navalny is a 2022 American documentary film directed by Daniel Roher.
The film revolves around Russian opposition leader Alexei
Navalny and events related to his poisoning.
It was produced by HBO Max and CNN Films.
The film premiered on January 25, 2022, at the Sundance Film Festival, where it received critical and audience
acclaim and won the Audience Award in the US Documentary competition and the Festival Favorite Award.
It also won the Best Documentary Feature at the 95th Academy Awards, won the award for Best Political Documentary at the
7th Critics' Choice Documentary Awards and picked up best documentary at the 76th BAFTA awards ceremony.
The film explores themes of biography, russian politics, russian
man, assassination attempt, russian secret police.